dailyrx.com 2015-09-12

# Privacy Policy | dailyRx

Updated April 23, 2014

This privacy policy describes how dailyRx, Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide dailyRx, [www.dailyRx.com](http://www.dailyrx.com/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number

We also collect the following information from you

  * Demographic information such as age, education, gender, interests and zip code
  * Health interests
  * When you download and use our mobile apps, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier (or "UDID").

We do not ask for, access or track any location-based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our mobile apps.

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We use this information to

  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis
  * Display content based upon your interests

## Choice/Opt-Out

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [info@dailyRx.com](mailto:info@dailyRx.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).

We enable you to create a profile, and share information such as messages, photos, and videos with others. Please note that we cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.

## Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Patient Conversation Media, Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

We share your personal information with other companies so that they can market their products or services to you. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at info@dailyRx.com.

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We use cookies on this site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personal information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site. The use of cookies by our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] is/is not covered by our privacy policy. We do/do not have access or control over these cookies.

 _Advertising_

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used to serve you targeted ads, you may opt-out of being served targeted ads by clicking here (<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

 _Web beacons_

Our Web pages may also contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that are set by our third party partners. Web beacons are used along with cookies enabling our partners to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used.  
We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

 _Local Shared Objects - Flash Cookies_

Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html>

_Links to Other Web Sites_

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of dailyRx, Inc.. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [info@dailyRx.com](mailto:info@dailyRx.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).

## Additional Policy Information

#### Email a Friend

If you choose to use our email a friend to tell a friend about an article, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the article. Patient Conversation Media does not store this information and is only used for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. Your friend may contact us at [info@dailyRx.com](mailto:info@dailyRx.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy) to request that we remove this information from our database.

#### Social Media Features and Widgets

Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ShareThis button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### Correcting, Deleting and Updating Your Personal Information

To review, delete or update your personal information, please contact us at [info@dailyRx.com](mailto:info@dailyRx.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. Please contact us if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### Notification of Privacy Policy Changes

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy policy by writing or email us at the address below:

 **dailyRx, Inc.**  
4315 Guadalupe Street  
Suite 200  
Austin, TX, United States 78751   
Email: [info@dailyRx.com](mailto:info@dailyRx.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy)
